You're a nerd in a field that you love, and you can act like a gentleman, and you're a witty, pompous guy.
I'm glad you're going back to your roots and wearing yellow-green for this week's costume. It was cherry blossom today.
You didn't get it? No, it's not. April 3rd.
It's been a year!
How's it going? How's it going?
A year? ! A year?
I know it seems like it's gone by in the blink of an eye, but...
But I've been able to do a lot of things I've never done before.
I've been able to do a lot of things I've never done before.
I'm very happy to have been able to discover something new, to have a new experience.
Who's the easiest to work with? No, no, no, no, I don't want to come here.
I'm not a kid.
DGP, of course.
DGP. Thank you very much.
You're running away from the only way out.
That's what I really thought.
I thought it was the only way out.
No, no, no, no, no...
It's terrible.
How do you feel about the dumpling buns?
A year ago, it was a new experience for me.
But it's still friendly.
It's the direction, isn't it? As a human being.
What do you mean by "direction"?
I thought you were closer to Ebichu in the sense of humanity.
Humanity.
So I didn't feel like, "What's going on? I don't know, I don't know.
I'm glad to hear that, huh?
I guess there are people like that.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
I see.
So it's easier to work with just the dumpling buns then? Of course.
That's good to hear. How's it going, Master?
Master, one year.
Oh, yeah...
But it doesn't feel like a year.
It doesn't feel like it's been that long.
I'm glad to hear that.
I also think you're very skillful in hanging around the staff.
I saw that.
I was watching.
I was watching them.
I'm pretty close to the end of the line.
Soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
From around here...
You're laughing so hard.
They're laughing all the time.
I can hear them having fun.
I'm having fun, thankfully.
I'm sure you're having more fun than the show itself.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
Well, something like that.
I mean, starting today.
You mean the start of the first anniversary.
That's what I mean.
Thank you for your continued support.
Just so you know...
Thank you very much.
Is there anything you're going to do for the first anniversary?
Let's do it!
Yes, but, well, I've finally figured out how to handle the master.
I've finally figured it out.
I'm starting to understand.
At first, you know...
I was like, "Wow!
I was like, "Wow, it's a rampaging horse!
Wait a minute, a rampaging horse is not a fish.
So you had the tazuna.
I was the horse and you were the tazuna type.
You're the tazuna. You're the tazuna man.
I'm going to do this properly and firmly.
I'll continue to do my best, and I look forward to working with you all as well.
By the way... this dancing Nippolyai Bouvaddick also sent me something interesting... and I found a picture he drew when he was a child at his parents' house.
I was surprised at the indescribable taste in his drawings, and I think he's looking at things with an honest eye, like he's grown up.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm already losing at this age... but my drawings are still good.
I watched it in real time when I was a kid.
I was really surprised at the name "Ultraman Tarou"... when I first saw it when I was a little kid... and the name was, relatively speaking... "Ultraman" or something like that.
Ultraman the Returned, Ultraman the Returned, Ultra 7... it's more of a katakana type name, you know?
But suddenly it was Ultraman Tarou, which is a very familiar name.
But the story was really interesting.
And the song, too... he sings "Taro" a lot... like "Taro, Taro, Taro, Taro, Ultraman Taro.
I see...
It brings back memories... the name's funny... that's right, it's funny... so the father... is not so normal.
Why not just call him Ultraman Daddy? He's the father of Ultraman.
I think it's a good name for him... but I'm surprised it's still around.
You remember... that's amazing.
It's a cute drawing with a crayon. I haven't had it for a long time.
When I go to my parents' house sometimes, I find a lot of crayons.
You used to draw things like riders.
And also...
At that time...
It was really popular at the time to imitate the signatures of Giants players.
There were a lot of autographs of players like Osadaji Ohsada and Osamu Nagashima.
I was practicing. I didn't get them.
All of them have me written on them.
You were practicing.
I wondered why I was so up-to-date.
You must have admired autographs like that.
It's cool, isn't it?
Well, well, well, well, well... that's all there is to it.
I'd like to visit this corner too.
May I?
Imagine the creatures!
Yes!
Here we go.
So, Mr. Monopoly, the expert shopper, sent me this again.
Thank you very much!
Uh, this time in Korean!
Korean!
That's surprisingly funny, isn't it?
No, I only understand Korean, Chuseoyo.
Hatik.
Me too... Makgeolli.
Makgeolli is delicious, isn't it?
Meatballs!
Samgyeopsal!
You said that the other day.
I can't remember it.
Why can't I remember anything but kimchi?
Kimchi.
Sundaebe
Samgyeta.
Samgeta
I've heard of it
Chukumi
What's that? A person's name
Idako
Cooking with sea cucumber
Daikon radish
yes
I mean...
May I?
It's in Korean.
I wonder...
Kokkiri.
It's like makgeolli.
Yes, it is.
Kokkkiri.
I don't know.
Well, well, well.
It's a very popular animal.
Popular
Yes, yes
Kokkiri.
Cocklebur.
Just the one and only.
Just this one.
Just 1,000 yen!
There's someone who understands.
I see.
Kokkiri!
Kokkiri.
It's okay to say "kokkiri".
Popular.
Kokkiri.
This one.
I wonder if there is a pronunciation for Korean too.
Oh, but I think there's something.
Like English.
Like "greed".
It's like "greedy" or something.
I used to learn it myself.
There are two ways to pronounce "o".
O?
Oto, which sounds like Japanese.
something like...
O?
It's quite difficult to pronounce, and sometimes it sounds a bit like Japanese.
Japanese used to have a lot more sounds.
There used to be more sounds in Japanese, too.
There were letters.
The active sounds are gradually being used more and more, and now they're not used anymore.
You know, there's a slithery thing under the "yoru"?
A house... like a house... like a house...
Do you have a grandmother who uses that character?
That's right.
It's a long time ago...
Yes...
Where do you want to go?
Let's go first.
If you serve first, you lose.
"Oishinbo" always loses.
So the second half is better.
The latter wins the ultimate showdown.
Well, it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
But if it does, I'll put it out for you.
Let's go first. My smallest one. This way.
Oh, my God! Do you see it?
Yes, yes...
Bitter and weak. I thought it might be a little weak.
You look a bit... No, it's a little weak.
I'm getting used to it. After a year...
I love how it sticks out like that.
I understand. You can't get caught in that kind of box anymore.
Who decides? Who decides? It's a frame.
Wow, it's a bit like a parrot, or a parrot-like parrot, I guess.
It's like a parrot, or a parrot-like parrot... like "How Do You Live?
Yes, it's very good!
It's an elephant!
That's right!
Very good!
It's an elephant!
I think elephants are...
I think they're really strange animals.
I mean...
It has a long nose.
It's quite an amazing looking animal.
It's a very surprising form.
But why is it so popular in zoos?
It has a nose with fangs.
It's kind of grotesque, isn't it?
I hear they're very smart.
I heard they're really smart. I want to ride an elephant.
I want to ride on it.
He's just about to walk on an elephant.
Or what? Or?
What kind of state is this?
He wants me to make a sentence with the cat statue.
I, Kenzo.
The players have stopped moving.
What do you mean? "Let's walk...
Bend your legs!
What's this?
Yearly elephant? My name is Year Elephant?
Yearly elephant?
Yearly Elephant.
You could be right.
You might be right.
Elephants live a very long time, don't they?
They do?
They do, don't they?
No, it's not.
Turtles... have a good image of longevity.
Turtles...
Killers live a thousand years, turtles live 10,000.
That's right.
Turtles live 10,000 years.
I don't think so, but they probably live longer than humans.
That's right.
That's pretty long.
You too, Mr. Shizou.
You'll have to hang in there.
Well, well, well... I guess we won't be doing the live broadcast anymore, huh?
You were up early today, weren't you? Yes, that's right.
Then... dumpling buns...
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching. How was it?
What did you think? Speaking of gyoza bread, recently...
I thought you said that was funny.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Maybe you haven't seen it. Maybe you need to see Kanna or Devil right now.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
There's a momentum in her voice. I know. I wonder what it is.
Tamamin, thank you for the Devil's Charge for Sarpon's 1st Anniversary!
And finally, Daikanai Devil, March 31st, it's almost here, but you've got to come.
No, no, no!
You're right.
So please put your tickets on the table now!
Tickets are on sale now. So, please take a look at this.
I feel like I want to go.
Also, Ramblow!
Random Bromide until March 31. Random bromides are like Gundam bromides, aren't they?
This is also available now until March 31, the very day of the Grand Viewing debut. I'm sure there are a lot of people who have already collected all of them, right?
I'm sure there are a lot of people who have already completed the list. But, you know, it's still random, so it's difficult to complete.
With Gundam, you know. There are a lot of Gundams. There are a lot of Gundams. Random is us.
So, we'll see you next week.
Next week? I hope to see you all again on the live feed.
Next week at 20:00.
I see.
But we'll see you next week, too. You have to watch it. No, no, no.
See you next week.
I forgot my apron. It was in the comments.